foreign
[Music]
walk with Iger I found the very first
spring flowers They're known as glory in
the snow and are a symbol of Happiness
warmth and fairy wishes I couldn't have
hoped for a Lovelier surprise the new
season has officially begun and I can
feel the renewal of life in my Valley
Through The Souls of my feet
[Music]
thank you
recently I've been spending a lot of
time alone there is something mystifying
about these cloudy days and April
Showers work has kept me busy and in my
free time I found myself wandering The
Woodlands losing all sense of the day
until the dust rolls in with my husband
away at work I'm in the company of our
growing family of animals a cat a dog
and two bunnies we make a ragtag group
thank you
[Music]
today reminded me a bit about when I was
living alone in my little cottage before
moving here I see more than enough
people living in more populated places
by homes in this area only to move away
quickly unable to handle the isolation
it certainly isn't the best environment
for everyone it makes me wonder if
finding peace is far more about the
interior world than without perhaps
living alone isn't really relevant more
living with ourselves
thank you
[Music]
I've been thinking about how different
my life is now that we're nearly at our
one year anniversary so much has changed
I learned quite a lot living single one
of them being the importance of not
isolating myself which can be easy to do
nestled in the foothills of a vast
mountain range
making the effort to go out working in
town or volunteering helps me stay
connected I think it is so important to
cultivate a nurturing space in our minds
to shift our practices from negativity
to Loving Thoughts honoring all our
emotions without letting unhelpful or
untrue mindsets consume us
I believe creating a loving space at
home does not involve things the perfect
apartment or best location it's about
the memories you associate with your
home you must fill your space with kind
thoughts and words acts of Love
friendship and life
it may take time to find people with
whom you connect but not all friends are
human my house full of dog hair and
houseplants is a testament to that
thank you
[Music]
I find it particularly important to have
a healthy perspective on the world
before choosing to live alone in an
isolated place
no matter how and where I've lived I
found keeping a positive outlook can be
tricky if you're consumed by negative
news stories or certain types of content
it is naturally important for me to stay
informed on what's going on in the world
the tragedies and Injustice it keeps me
caring deeply and taking action in small
ways I'm able but I find it is crucial
to balance out what I consume with
positive news happening in the world and
my local community which interesting
enough tend to rarely make the headlines
I can only assume it's because as humans
we seem to fixate on negative
information
more willing to let those harsh truths
affect our reality than more hopeful
perspectives about our world in the
future I find as I grow older it's so
much easier to honor my negative
emotions and experiences while not
allowing them to Define me and my world
view
[Music]
thank you
I saw a tutorial online on how to do
this and apparently it is a tradition
associated with Japan it is called
kokedama I want to say but I'm probably
butchering that term however I saw
pictures online of these Moss balls and
I just thought they were so strange and
interesting and this plant is going to
get quite big and bushy and so I thought
it will after a few months hopefully
offset the kind of largeness of the
bottom here is an idea for a really
simple way to pot your plants it is
pretty inexpensive you just really need
moss and a bit of wire and some string
and it's really lovely and it drains
really well too which is always an added
benefit so if you want your home to feel
like a forest fairy Wonderland or an
enchanted witch's Garden or whatever
else you're going for here is a fun idea
I have accepted that my taste in home
decor is um uh on unconventional to say
the least
[Music]
thank you it's not an easy path to take
to shift perspective and believe in
something better I fail often but it has
helped me love more freely and let go of
a lot of judgment once you begin to see
the world as full of an abundance of
love that love becomes magnified and
even in the darkest of places it is
still there though it can be easy to
overlook
for quite a few years of my young adult
life especially after leaving an abusive
relationship I stubbornly nursed my
victimhood and was unwilling to open
myself to love from new people and to
heal
if I'd made that into a habit I would
have never thrived living alone or
eventually meant my husband
maybe none of this is helpful to you
we're all different and I don't know
what works for you but I thought I'd
share some last memories of my days
living alone before starting my second
year of married life perhaps at the end
of the day it doesn't matter how you
live more have you love take care
foreign
[Music]
so I left the biggest mess in the house
it is absolute chaos here right now
because I was working on that planter
and I left
um moss in a dish and my cat mavi
decided to throw the Moss all around the
house and so in an attempt to
procrastinate I thought I would chat
with you guys a little bit in this one
clean corner of the room as an update a
couple months ago I made a little
terrarium and it's doing really really
well I think I'll have to open the top
in a little bit to let the little plant
grow a little more but I just wanted to
give an update on that I also have this
vanilla bean extract just in alcohol
that is brewing and it's only been
brewing for a few weeks now so it's
definitely going to get a lot darker and
richer as time goes on so so it's going
to be about
six more months I think of letting it
kind of sit in weight but it is going to
be delicious I found my very first
flowers on my walk today it was so
exciting I cannot wait because what is
coming next are the spring beauties and
they are always some of the first
flowers that come up besides the
buttercups and then the little blue
bells come up as well I am waiting in
great anticipation thank you so much for
all the support on my Etsy shop by the
couple new listings and I'm working on
some new projects and so I appreciate
all your feedback contact me anytime
with any issues never be shy and I am
more than happy to help you so thank you
again and I'm sending all of you my love
and I will see you soon
bye
[Music]
foreign